Contato

351913460479 (Mobile) wendellwoneys@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/wendellwoney (LinkedIn)

wendellwoney.github.io (Personal)

Principais competências

Scrum

PHP

PostgreSQL

Certifications

Iniciando com ASP.NET Core

SFC Scrum Fundamentals Certified

C: conhecendo a Linguagem das Linguagens

PHP boas práticas

C: RECURSOS AVANÇADOS DA LINGUAGEM

Wendell Woney

Developer PHP, JAVA, C#, NodeJS

Vila Nova de Gaia, Porto, Portugal

Resumo

Graduated in Information Systems Management, I have been working as a developer since 2008. I have experience in PHP, JAVA, NodeJS, C# using the MYSQL, MariaDB, POSTGRES, SqlLite, SQLSERVER databases. Let's talk?

GitHub - https://github.com/wendellwoney

Experiência

RETAIL4PEOPLE

Desenvolvedor de sistemas Java outubro de 2022 - Present (3 meses)

Porto, Portugal

IBTech IT Solutions

2 anos 3 meses

Senior Developer PHP, JAVA, C#, NodeJS outubro de 2020 - Present (2 anos 3 meses)

Jaraguá do sul, Santa Catarina, Brasil

I work as a senior developer with a greater focus on the backend, responsible for planning and creating new services. Working on the company's main products for B2B platforms, using PHP, JAVA, C# and NodeJS, Docker, MariaDB and Postgres database technologies.

It is part of my day to day to ensure the quality of the code with good practices and also the availability and scalability of services.

Senior Developer PHP, JAVA, C#, NodeJS | Product Owner outubro de 2021 - setembro de 2022 (1 ano)

Jaraguá do sul, Santa Catarina, Brasil

Along with the developer work already done, I also act as Product Owner of the B2B tool.

As P.O I work in the construction, improvement and maintainer of the team's Backlog, coordinating and managing the Sprints planning meetings, I follow the Product Backlog items to achieve the stipulated goals, optimizing the value of the work delivered by the development team, ensuring the product delivery quality.

Avansys Tecnologia Analista de sistemas fevereiro de 2011 - outubro de 2020 (9 anos 9 meses)

Development and implementation of systems, dimensioning system requirements and functionality, helping to specify its architecture, choosing development tools, specifying programs, coding applications.

Alfama Web
Desenvolvedor da web
outubro de 2008 - janeiro de 2011 (2 anos 4 meses)

Formação acadêmica

Instituto Brasileiro de Formação - IBF Pós MBA BIG DATA, Tecnologia da Informação · (2019 - 2020)

FANESE - Faculdade de Administração e Negócios de Sergipe Gestão de Tecnologia da Informação · (2005 - 2008)